seanogle.com 2019-07-17

# Privacy Policy - Location Rebel

This privacy policy sets out how **Location Rebel** uses and protects any information that you give **Location Rebel** when you use this website.

 **Location Rebel** is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

 **Location Rebel** may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from April 18, 2011.

 **What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

  * name and job title
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

 **What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

 **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

 **Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

 **Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at **sean@locationrebel.com**
  * You may also unsubscribe from any of our emails or mailings by hitting the unsubscribe button at the end of every email.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

 **Updating Your Personal Information and Privacy Preferences**

You have the right to access and correct, or delete your personal information at any time. Upon request, Location Rebel will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personal information. To make a request for this information, please contact us at sean@locationrebel.com

If you wish to request that we no longer use your information to provide you with services, please contact us at sean@locationrebel.com. We will respond to your request within 30 days. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

 **Privacy Complaints**

Individuals located in certain countries, including the European Economic Area, have certain statutory rights in relation to their personal data. Subject to any exemptions provided by law, you may have the right to request access to your personal information held by Location Rebel, as well as to seek to update, delete or correct that information.

To the extent that Location Rebel’s processing of your personal information is subject to the EU General Data Protection Regulation, Location Rebel relies on its legitimate interests, described above, to process your data. Where Location Rebel processes certain personal information for its own direct marketing purposes, you have a right to object to Location Rebel’s use of your personal information for this purpose at any time by emailing sean@locationrebel.com.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this SITE, or your dealings with this SITE, you can contact our Data Protection Officer at sean@locationrebel.com
